[Music]
hello everyone this is Rahul Zaria from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stock
updates 3 basically means right sector
right quality and right valuation this
are our investment
ideas today we have an update on
biocon we are upgrading biocon to buy
from hold because won biologics is
improving its performance led by
acquisition of VRI and for the success
full integration of vri's business into
biocon for 120 countries the operational
performance is likely to be offset by
higher cost like Finance cost due to
debt taken to finance the V Day We
Believe Management is confidence of
repaying debt by divesting its non-core
assets and bringing down net debt to AA
to three times by fi 26 from six times
currently in fi23 going forward we
believe there are many green shoots in
the company such as lower R of debt to
reduce Finance cost increased market
share of bio similars post the
successful integration of vatri business
and pick up in the generic API segment
driven by complex launches in the
peptide space hence we upgrade the stock
to buy from hold earlier we value biogon
on ANP basis when in the generic segment
Singin and biologics business on an EV
by ABA basis of five times 19 times and
seven times respectively on fi 26
earnings to arrive at a Target price of
R 335 per share we would also like to
value the stock on price to equity basis
by allting a price to equity of 22 times
on FY 26 estimated EPS of rupe 15 per
share to arrive at a price target of R
330 per share we would like to allot 50%
weighted to GOP and price to equity
metrologies to arrive at a price target
of R 332 per
share next we have an update on icsi
Lombard our analyst maintains buy rating
on icsi Lombard with a price target of R
1740 the company reported healthy
numbers in quarter 3 underwriting loss
fell by 4% year on-ear on the back of
lower combined ratio and healthy net ear
premium the company has maintained a
guidance of a high team growth in
premium while combined ratio is expected
to fall further to 102% by FY 25 we
expect strong premium growth led by
investment in distribution Channel and
leveraging digital capabilities gradual
Improvement in combin ratios should
boost profitability further we expect
the company to deliver medium-term Roe
of 18% at the current market price the
stock trades at 30.4 di F525 and 25.5 di
FY 26 estimated EPS the stock has
underperformed the broader indices in
last 12
months for more detailed disclosures and
disclaimers please refer to our research
report or contact our nearest
Brands please read the risk Disclosure
document issued by SEI and relevant
exchanges and terms and condition on
sharon.com before
investing
thank you for watching to keep up with
the latest from sherhan make sure you
subscribe to our Channel you can also
download the sharan app for all your
trading and investing
[Music]
needs investment and securities Market
are subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing